# YUSUKE KOMINAMI

#### +81-90-6199-9337

yukke.konan@gmail.com

## **Education**

## **Kyoto University**

B.S. Biology (Mar 2020)

Main area: Bioinformatics and image processing with machine learning.

Research: research theme is super resolution of images taken with electronic microscope.

Swiss Federal
Institute of
Technology in
Lausanne, faculty of
Computer Science

AugStudy abroad (Aug 2018 - Dec 2018)

#### **Skills**

- Algorithm design for machine learning.
- Project Management
- Python, Common Lisp, Java, etc.

### **Profile**

I am Yusuke Kominami. I graduated from the faculty of Science in Kyoto University, majored Biology. About software engineering, my expertise ranges from HTML/CSS/JavaScript to low-level programming. And I have solid knowledge on machine learning and statistics based on mathematics.

## **Experience**

**SoftBank** — April, 2020 - Present Machine Learning Engineer, building a

Aiful - May, 2019 - Present

Software Engineer and Project Manager. As a part-time worker, building office system with Python with Django and GCP.

LINE - August, 2019

Summer Internship. Made a small Web application in a week.

Flywheel — August, 2019 - September, 2019

Summer Internship: Data Scientist and Machine Learning Engineer. Built a recommendation algorithm in LOHACO and optimized advertisement delivery system.

ABEJA - June, 2019 - July, 2019

Machine Learning Intern. Implemented object detection algorithms.

Hitachi — June, 2017 - July, 2018

Machine Learning Research Intern. Main area was Reinforcement Learning.

### Links

GitHub: https://github.com/komi1230

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/yusuke-kominami-0419b1157/

Portfolio: https://komi1230.github.io

Twitter: https://twitter.com/komi\_edtr\_1230